<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Authors on muleML</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/en/author/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Authors on muleML</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/en/author/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Andrea Maurano</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/author/andrea-maurano/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/author/andrea-maurano/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Physicist and materials engineer, PhD at Imperial College London and post-doc at MIT in Boston. He worked as a researcher in the US at MIT, Samsung, and 24M labs, exploring batteries, photonics, and artificial intelligence. Back in Italy, he founded muleML — where he now serves as Scientific Advisor — with a simple goal: making energy more reliable and sustainable, and proving that even the most complex research can still have a smiling face.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Francesco Falcolini</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/author/francesco-falcolini/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/author/francesco-falcolini/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Physicist, with his head always among data, algorithms, and batteries. After a long career leading projects in banking, business, healthcare, and public administration, he founded muleML, where he serves as CEO. He believes predictive models should be explainable, useful, and sustainable — and when in doubt, he always prefers a concrete approach over a trendy buzzword.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>muleML Editorial Team</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/author/muleml-editorial-team/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/author/muleml-editorial-team/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;hellip;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pietro Portolani</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/author/pietro-portolani/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/author/pietro-portolani/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Co-founder and CTO of muleML, a mechanical engineer “converted” to computer science. With a PhD from Politecnico di Milano and years of experience in industrial research and AI, today he leads the company’s technological development. He sees in data and algorithms the key to understanding the complexity around us and making our future more sustainable.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
